I haven't seen you in ages, Marcus.
You look like you've been through hell.
Tell your sister to break a leg
before the show tonight.
I'll meet you by the bank at noon.
Bring the documents.
No, not the river bank —
the one on Fifth Avenue.
Oh, great. Just great.
Relax, this'll be a piece of cake.
It's raining cats and dogs out there.
Did you bring an umbrella?
The server is down. We need to reboot
the firewall before the meeting.
I'll grab a coffee at Starbucks
and meet you at Penn Station.
We have a mole in the department.
Someone's been leaking information.
The suspect said they would cooperate,
but their lawyer disagreed.
Take the light bag, not the heavy one.
Your Honor, my client, Mr. O'Brien,
has cooperated fully.
I knew you'd come through, kid.
Don't get cold feet now.
If anyone asks, you were never here.
Understood?
We need 10 milligrams of adrenaline,
stat!
Damn it, Marcus!
Whatever happens tonight...
remember, I've always had your back.